I do hope the economy recovers you know
a lot of people are worried about the
economy right now they're worried about
how they're doing economically how
they're doing financially uh but don't
worry I figured out a perfect way to
tell where you stand economically it all
depends on how you feel about Red
Lobster
if you think Red Lobster is a fancy
restaurant you're not doing well
economically
[Laughter]
what a fancy restaurant it's Applebee's
plus Lobster
the thing they're most famous for is
their Cheddar Bay Biscuits which is
weird because if you serve lobster but
you're more famous for the free bread
you left on the table
you are not making the lobster correctly
[Laughter]
it's really nice to be back on the road
for stand up whenever I'm on the road I
try to travel cheap so I stay at Motel 6
a lot
and then some nights I'm in the mood for
something a little cleaner and classier
and I just sleep in the car
fixes like the Red Lobster of hotels
I don't mind staying in a different
Motel every night but then I have to
figure out how a different shower works
every morning it always makes me feel
like I'm a lab rat in some sort of cruel
experiment I'm just standing there naked
and scared in front of a bunch of
buttons and levers and I know that one
of them will punish me with hot water
and one of them will punish me with cold
water but if I can figure out the code
I'll get some warm water
foreign
of course the whole experiment's being
timed because if you don't figure it out
by 9am and get downstairs they take away
breakfast and you don't get any cheese
[Applause]
when I flew in here I got to sit in the
exit row on the plane they always ask me
that question where they're like are you
willing and able to help in an emergency
and I don't know if I could do it but I
always say yes
because if I fail No One's Gonna live to
tell about it
[Applause]
I groom worst case scenario you die
slightly more comfortable than the
people behind you
[Laughter]
the flight I was on a flight and this
guy was sitting in front of me and the
flight attendant comes over and she goes
sir are you willing and able to help in
an emergency and he goes no no and she
goes well then I'm gonna have to ask you
to move I need a verbal yes in order to
sit here and he goes okay yes
really
you just temporarily forgot that you can
save 180 lives if need be
but uh I flew back to uh Pennsylvania
once last year that was the time I was
on a flight to see a friend of mine who
just became a father and uh like all new
parents he pretends that he likes
fatherhood but I can tell he's sick of
it just by the way he talks about the
baby
you know it's great she's so cute but
she wakes up at 3am every night to feed
there's like nothing that you love feeds
and vampires and parasites feed
things that suck the life out of you
nobody talks that way about something
they love it's never like oh me and my
wife just celebrated our one year
anniversary I took her to Red Lobster so
she could feed
hey thanks for watching uh please be
sure to download the dry bar app and
when you do use my promo code Adam
yenser you can also try my promo code at
Subway or Applebee's it won't work but
I'd like you to try it